Melville S. Munro Papers MS036
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographic history of Tufts College, 1904 -- 1946; MS036.001; 20.8 Linear Feet; 329 Digital Object(s)
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 10, 1924-11 -- 1925-03; MS036.001.010.00001 (Volume 10)
    - Class of 1925 in front of Eaton Hall, February 16, MS036.001.010.00001.04276; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 10)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 10, p. 42, #4698
    - Class of 1925 in front of Eaton Hall, February 16, MS036.001.010.00001.04277; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 10)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 10, p. 43, #4699
    - Boxing class, February 18, 1925; MS036.001.010.00001.04278; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 10)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 010, p. 54, #4717
      Students; Boxing; Men; Athletics; photographic print; Black students
    - Boxing class, February 18, 1925; MS036.001.010.00001.04279; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 10)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 010, p. 55, #4718
      Students; Men; Boxing; Athletics; photographic print; Black students
    - Boxing class, February 18, 1925; MS036.001.010.00001.04280; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 10)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 010, p. 55, #4721
    - Boxing class, February 18, 1925; MS036.001.010.00001.04281; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 10)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 010, p. 56, #4720
    - Ye East Hall Gang in front of East Hall, February 24, 1925; MS036.001.010.00001.04282; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 10)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 010, p. 58, #4731
    - Ye East Hall Gang in front of East Hall, February 24, 1925; MS036.001.010.00001.04283; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 10)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 010, p. 59, #4732
    - Track squad, March 10, 1925; MS036.001.010.00001.04284; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 10)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 010, p.105, #4835
      Students; Athletics; Track (Men's); photographic print; Black students
    - Class of 1927 in front of Eaton Hall, March 13, 1925; MS036.001.010.00001.04285; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 10)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 010, p.141, #4866
    - Class of 1927 in front of Eaton Hall, March 13, 1925; MS036.001.010.00001.04286; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 10)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 010, p.142, #4867
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 11, 1925-03 -- 1925-12; MS036.001.028.00001 (Volume 28)
    House party photos of Alpha Tau Omega pg 18
    - Unidentified Tufts baseball player, 1925; MS036.001.028.00001.00102; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 28)
      Munro Scrapbook, vol. 11, p. 58, photograph #9407
      Athletics; Baseball; People; Students; copy negative; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics
    - Class of 1928 in front of Eaton Hall, March, 1925; MS036.001.028.00001.04287; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 28)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 028, p.2, #4874
    - Class of 1928 in front of Eaton Hall, March, 1925; MS036.001.028.00001.04288; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 28)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 028, p.3, #4875
    - Tufts track squad, June 3, 1925; MS036.001.028.00001.04289; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 28)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 028, p. 72, #5028
    - Tufts track squad, June 3, 1925; MS036.001.028.00001.04290; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 28)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 028, p. 73, #5029
    - Tufts varsity track team, June 3, 1925; MS036.001.028.00001.04317; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 28)
      Print is in the Munro Collection, Box 028, p. 74, #5030
    - Tufts varsity track team, June 3, 1925; MS036.001.028.00001.04318; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 28)
      Print is in the Munro Collection, Box 028, p. 74, #5031
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 4, Miscellaneous Views, 1913 -- 1927; MS036.001.029.00001 (Volume 29)
    - George Henson with a horse and buggy in front of Eaton Hall, 1917-03-30; MS036.001.029.00001.01129; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 29)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 4, Box No. 29, Pg. 76 - "Miscellaneous Views Prior to 1927."
      People; Buildings; photographic print; Henson, George Wiseman
    - Registrar Nellie Alvira Wright, 1920; MS036.001.029.00001.01824; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 29)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 4, Box No. 29, Pg. 145 - "Miscellaneous Views Prior to 1927"
      People; Staff; photographic print; Wright, Nellie Alvira
    - Mr. Brosnahan as clerk, 1924-09-03; MS036.001.029.00001.02955; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 29)
      Photographic History of Tufts College, box 29, p. 30.
      Post offices; photographic print; Tufts College
    - Mr. Brosnahan as [mail] carrier, 1916-05-26; MS036.001.029.00001.02956; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 29)
      Letter carriers; photographic print; Tufts College
    - Professor Albert Hatton Gilmer, 1922; MS036.001.029.00001.03333; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 105)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 4 - Misc. Views, Box No. 29, Pg. 68
      People; Faculty; photographic print; Gilmer, Albert Hatton; Dept. of English
    - Secretary of Commerce Herbert Hoover speaking to faculty members, 1920-06-21; MS036.001.029.00001.03454; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 76)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol 4, Box 29, Pg. 76 - "Miscellaneous Views Prior to 1927."
      People; Faculty; photographic print; Hoover, Herbert C.; U.S. Department of Commerce
    - Assistant in the College Office Wilhelmine Hazel Langdell (left) and Registrar Nellie Alvira Wright (right), 1913; MS036.001.029.00001.03456; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 29)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 4, Box No. 29, Pg. 145 - "Miscellaneous Views Prior to 1927."
      People; Staff; photographic print; Langdell, Wilhelmine Hazel; Wright, Nellie Alvira; Office of the Registrar
    - Wilhelmine Langdell (left) and Nellie Wright (right), 1913; MS036.001.029.00001.03457; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 29)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol 4, Box No. 29, Pg. 145 - "Miscellaneous Views Prior to 1927."
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 12, 1925-12 -- 1926-06; MS036.001.030.00001 (Volume 30)
    Alpha Omicron Pi photos of members, p100-101; House party photos of Alpha Tau Omega, p 68-70
    - Dramatics production, 1926 -- 1929; MS036.001.030.00001.00910; Unknown (Volume 30)
      5 photo (dated May 22, 1926) contained in Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 12, Box No. 30, Pg. 119
      People; Students; Theater; photographic print; Dept. of Drama
    - Instructor of English Ruth Tousey, 1926-06-02; MS036.001.030.00001.03337; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 30)
      Vol 12, Box No. 30, Pg. 144
      People; Faculty; photographic print; Tousey, Ruth; Dept. of English
    - Dramatics production, 1926-05-22; MS036.001.030.00001.03481; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 30)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 12, Box No. 30, Pg. 119
    - Jackson College students in front of Eaton Hall, 1926-05-19; MS036.001.030.00001.04304; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 30)
      Print is in the Munro Collection, Box 030, p. 109, #5541
      Women; Students; photographic print; Black students; Jackson College
    - Ye East Hall Gang, 1926-05-21; MS036.001.030.00001.04305; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 30)
      Print is in the Munro Collection, Box 030, p. 112, #5546
    - Ye East Hall Gang, 1926-05-21; MS036.001.030.00001.04306; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 30)
      Print is in the Munro Collection, Box 030, p. 113, #5547
    - Tufts track squad in front of Barnum Hall, 1926-06-02; MS036.001.030.00001.04307; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 30)
      Print is in the Munro Collection, Box 030, p. 146, #5586
    - Tufts track squad in front of Barnum Hall, 1926-06-02; MS036.001.030.00001.04308; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 30)
      Print is in the Munro Collection, Box 030, p. 147, #5587
    - Tufts track squad in front of Barnum Hall, 1926-06-02; MS036.001.030.00001.04309; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 30)
      Print is in the Munro Collection, Box 030, p. 148, #5588
    - Tufts varsity track "T" men in front of Barnum Hall, 1926-06-02; MS036.001.030.00001.04310; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 30)
      Print is in the Munro Collection, Box 030, p. 150, #5589
    - Tufts varsity track "T" men in front of Barnum Hall, 1926-06-02; MS036.001.030.00001.04311; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 30)
      Print is in the Munro Collection, Box 030, p. 151, #5590
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 13, 1926-06 -- 1927-02; MS036.001.031.00001 (Volume 31)
    Alpha Tau Omega photos of members, 104-105, 113-114; Alumni day, pp 6-7
    - Faculty leading the commencement procession, 1926-06-14; MS036.001.031.00001.01692; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 31)
      (found in Photographic History of Tufts, Volume XIII, pg. 20, box 031)
      Commencement; photographic print
    - The commencement procession, 1926-06-14; MS036.001.031.00001.01693; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 31)
      (found in Photographic History of Tufts, Volume XIII, pg. 22, box 031)
    - Members of Tufts football team, 1925-06-23; MS036.001.031.00001.01694; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 31)
      (found in Photographic History of Tufts, Volume XIII, pg. 22, #5805, box 031)
      Athletics; Football; photographic print
    - The Jumbonians, 1926-06-14; MS036.001.031.00001.02718; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 31)
      Photographic History of Tufts, Vol. 13: Box 31, pg 17
      People; Student activities; photographic print; The Jumbonians
    - Sidney Lutzin (4'11") and Lester Adelson (6'6"), 1931-10-30; MS036.001.031.00001.03336; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 50)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 31, Box No. 50, Pg. 105
      People; Students; photographic print; Lutzin, Sidney; Adelson, Lester
    - Tufts football team A, 1926-09-23; MS036.001.031.00001.04291; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 31)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 031, p. 46, #5800
    - Tufts football squad, 1926-09-23; MS036.001.031.00001.04292; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 31)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 031, p. 66, #5797
    - Tufts football team, 1926-09-23; MS036.001.031.00001.04293; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 31)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 031, p. 69, #5798
      Students; Athletics; Football; photographic print; Black students
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 14, 1927 -- 1928; MS036.001.032.00001 (Volume 32)
    Alpha Xi Delta photos of members, 38-39; Alpha Omicron Pi photos of members, p20-21. Alpha Tau Omega photos of members, p82
    - Jackson field hockey squad, February 25, 1924; MS036.001.032.00001.04294; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 32)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 032, p. 36, #5996
      Students; Women; Field Hockey; photographic print; Black students; Jackson College
    - Tufts class of 1927 in front of Goddard Chapel, 1927-02-28; MS036.001.032.00001.04295; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 32)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 032, p. 48, #6007
    - Tufts class of 1927 in front of Goddard Chapel, 1927-02-28; MS036.001.032.00001.04296; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 32)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 032, p. 49, #6008
    - Jackson College, class of 1927 in front of Barnum Hall, 1927-03-05; MS036.001.032.00001.04297; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 32)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 032, p. 51, #6036
    - Jackson College, class of 1927 in front of Barnum Hall, 1927-03-05; MS036.001.032.00001.04298; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 32)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 032, p.52, #6034
    - Jackson College, class of 1927 in front of Barnum Hall, 1927-03-05; MS036.001.032.00001.04299; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 32)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 032, p.53, #6035
    - Jackson College, class of 1927 in front of Goddard Chapel, 1927-02-28; MS036.001.032.00001.04300; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 32)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 032, p.54, #6023
    - Jackson College, class of 1927 in front of Goddard Chapel, 1927-02-28; MS036.001.032.00001.04301; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 32)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 032, p.55, #6024
    - Claude Randolph Taylor, class of 1927, MS036.001.032.00001.04302; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 32)
      Print is in the Munro Collection, Box 032, p. 65, #6045
      Students; Men; photographic print; Black students; Taylor, Claude Randolph
    - Claude Randolph Taylor, class of 1927, MS036.001.032.00001.04303; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 32)
      Print is in the Munro Collection, Box 032, p. 65, #6044
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 15, 1927-04 -- 1927-10; MS036.001.033.00001 (Volume 33)
    Alumni day
    - Tufts team captains, 1927-06-08; MS036.001.033.00001.03331; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 33)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 15, Box No. 33, Pg. 65; left to right: Charles Stevens, Irving Garcelon, Allen Lester, Henry Bagley, Clarence Stanley
      People; Students; Athletics; photographic print; Stevens, Charles R.; Garcelon, Irving; Lester, Allen; Bagley, Henry; Stanley, Clarence; Wrestling; Baseball; Track; Men's basketball team
    - Two men standing near a construction site on "The Hill" with Goddard Chapel in the background, 1930; MS036.001.033.00001.03463; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 33)
      Munro scrapbook: Vol. 15, Box 33, Pg. 109
      People; Views; Buildings; Chapels; photographic print
    - Tufts track squad in front of Goddard Chapel, 1927-06-08; MS036.001.033.00001.04312; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 33)
      Print is in the Munro Collection, Box 033, p. 67, #6335
    - Tufts track squad in front of Goddard Chapel, 1927-06-08; MS036.001.033.00001.04313; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 33)
      Print is in the Munro Collection, Box 033, p. 68, #6336
    - Tufts track squad in front of Goddard Chapel, 1927-06-08; MS036.001.033.00001.04314; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 33)
      Print is in the Munro Collection, Box 033, p. 69, #6337
    - Class Day procession, Ballou Hall, 1927-06-18; MS036.001.033.00001.04315; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 33)
      Print is in the Munro Collection, Box 033, p. 88, #6367
      Students; Commencement; Processions; photographic print; Black students
    - Tufts freshman football squad, 1927-09-26; MS036.001.033.00001.04316; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 33)
      Print is in the Munro Collection, Box 033, p. 127, #6423
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 16, 1927-10 -- 1927-12; MS036.001.034.00001 (Volume 34)
    - H. Glick, Jeaster Hairston, G. S. MacCullum, H. Hecker, and G. A. Connolly, Jr., 1927; MS036.001.034.00001.04319; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 34)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 34, #6459, p. 2
      Students; photographic print; Black students; Glick, H.; Hairston, Jester; MacCallum, G. S.; Hecker, H.; Connolly, G. A., Jr.
    - J. E. Moseley, C. E. Marron, J. K. Hoban, F. H. Case, Jr. and W. E. Stone, 1927; MS036.001.034.00001.04320; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 34)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 34, #6453, p. 3
      Students; photographic print; Black students; Moseley, J. E.; Marron, C. E.; Hoban, J. K.; Case, F. H., Jr.; Stone, W. E.
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 72, 1941-03 -- 1941-05; MS036.001.035.00001; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 35)
    [Alumni] Classification index cards for Tufts Alumni Directory, p139
    - Eddie Dugger, 1939; MS036.001.035.00001.03347; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 35)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 72, Box No. 35, Pg. 121
      People; Athletics; Track (Men's); photographic print; Dugger, Edward
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 22, 1929-01 -- 1929-03; MS036.001.036.00001; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 36)
    - The Shenley Four, 1929-02-10; MS036.001.036.00001.02717; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 63)
      Photographic History of Tufts, Vol. 22: box 36, pg. 16
      People; Student activities; photographic print; Hairston, Jester; Ayers, Lucien; Carter, Theodore; Barrow, Herbert; The Shenley Four
    - Intercollegiate wrestling champions, 1929-03-22; MS036.001.036.00001.02960; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 36)
      Photographic History of Tufts College, Vol. 22, box 36, Pg. 131. Left to right: Frank Stella, 115 pound class, Charles E. Hingston, 175 pound class, Irving G. Gareelon, 125 pound class.
      Athletics; Wrestling; photographic print; Stella, Frank; Hingston, Charles E.; Garcelon, Irving
    - Hairston's Quartet or the Shenley Four, 1929-02-10; MS036.001.036.00001.03346; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 36)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 22, Box No. 36, Pg. 17
      People; Students; Student activities; photographic print; Barrow, Herbert; Carter, Theodore; Ayers, Lucien; Hairston, Jester; The Shenley Four
    - Tufts golf team, 1929-03-01; MS036.001.036.00001.03474; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 36)
      MS036/001-036, p. 85-86.
      People; Students; Athletics; Golf; photographic print
    - The Shenley Four: Herbert Barrow, Theodore Carter, Lucien Ayers, and Jester Hairston, 1929-02-10; MS036.001.036.00001.04321; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 36)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 36, #7814, p. 16
      Students; photographic print; Black students; Barrow, Herbert; Carter, Theodore; Ayers, Lucien; Hairston, Jester; Shenley Four
    - The Shenley Four: Herbert Barrow, Theodore Carter, Lucien Ayers, and Jester Hairston, 1929-02-10; MS036.001.036.00001.04322; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 36)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 36, #7815, p. 17
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 20, 1928-09 -- 1928-11; MS036.001.037.00001 (Volume 37)
    - Jack Moody, "The Sandwich Man", 1928-11-02; MS036.001.037.00001.02957; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 37)
      Photographic History of Tufts College, Vol. 20, Box No. 37, Pg. 131
      Food service; photographic print; Moody, Jack
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 21, 1928-11 -- 1929-01; MS036.001.038.00001 (Volume 38)
    - From Emperor Jones, Scene VII, 1928-12-14; MS036.001.038.00001.02947; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 38)
      Photographic History of Tufts College volume 21, pg. 87
      Student activities; photographic print
    - Fred Derby, 1928-12-16; MS036.001.038.00001.03338; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 38)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 21, Box No. 38, Pg. 118
      People; Staff; photographic print; Derby, Fred; Tufts Police
    - Charlie of the Golf Course, 1928-12-24; MS036.001.038.00001.03339; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 38)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 21, Box No. 38, Pg. 142
      People; Staff; Golf; photographic print
    - Dr. Frank W. Durkee, 1929-01-12; MS036.001.038.00001.03455; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 38)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol 21, Box No. 38, Pg. 148
      People; Faculty; photographic print; Durkee, Frank W.; Dept. of Chemistry
    - John Moseley and Dorman Hayes in Scene I from Emperor Jones, 1928-12-14; MS036.001.038.00001.04341; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 38)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 38 p. 71, #7719
      Students; Plays; photographic print; Black students; Moseley, John. E.; Hayes, Dorman
    - John Moseley and Dorman Hayes in Scene I from Emperor Jones, 1928-12-14; MS036.001.038.00001.04342; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 38)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 38 p. 72, #7720
    - John Moseley and Dorman Hayes in Scene I from Emperor Jones, 1928-12-14; MS036.001.038.00001.04343; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 38)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 38 p. 73, #7721
    - John Moseley in Scene IV from Emperor Jones, 1928-12-14; MS036.001.038.00001.04344; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 38)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 38 p. 75, #7723
      Students; Plays; photographic print; Black students; Moseley, John. E.
    - Scene IV from Emperor Jones, 1928-12-14; MS036.001.038.00001.04345; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 38)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 38 p. 76, #7724
      Students; Plays; photographic print; Black students
    - Scene V from Emperor Jones, 1928-12-14; MS036.001.038.00001.04346; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 38)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 38 p. 77, #7725
    - Scene V from Emperor Jones, 1928-12-14; MS036.001.038.00001.04347; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 38)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 38 p. 78, #7726
    - Scene V from Emperor Jones, 1928-12-14; MS036.001.038.00001.04348; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 38)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 38 p. 79, #7727
    - Scene VI from Emperor Jones, 1928-12-14; MS036.001.038.00001.04349; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 38)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 38 p. 81, #7729
    - Jester Hairston, Scene VII, from Emperor Jones, 1928-12-14; MS036.001.038.00001.04350; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 38)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 38 p. 82, #7730
      Students; Plays; photographic print; Black students; Hairston, Jester
    - Scene VII from Emperor Jones, 1928-12-14; MS036.001.038.00001.04351; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 38)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 38 p. 83, #7731
    - Jester Hairston and John Moseley, in Scene VII in Emperor Jones, 1928-12-14; MS036.001.038.00001.04352; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 38)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 38 p. 84, #7732
      Students; Plays; photographic print; Black students; Hairston, Jester; Moseley, John. E.
    - Jester Hairston and John Moseley, in Scene VII in Emperor Jones, 1928-12-14; MS036.001.038.00001.04353; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 38)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 38 p. 85, #7733
    - Jester Hairston and John Moseley, in Scene VII in Emperor Jones, 1928-12-14; MS036.001.038.00001.04354; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 38)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 38 p. 86, #7734
    - Jester Hairston, detail pose for makeup for Emperor Jones, 1928-12-14; MS036.001.038.00001.04355; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 38)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 38 p. 87, #7735
    - Jester Hairston, detail pose for makeup for Emperor Jones, 1928-12-14; MS036.001.038.00001.04356; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 38)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 38 p. 88, #7736
    - John Moseley, Jester Hairston, and Dorman Hayes, Scene VIII, from Emperor Jones, 1928-12-14; MS036.001.038.00001.04357; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 38)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 38 p. 90, #7738
      Students; Plays; photographic print; Black students; Moseley, John. E.; Hairston, Jester; Hayes, Dorman
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 19, 1928-04 -- 1928-06; MS036.001.039.00001; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 39)
    - Tufts pitcher Edward W. Smith, 1928-06-08; MS036.001.039.00001.03345; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 39)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 19, Box No. 39, Pg. 89
      People; Students; Athletics; Baseball; photographic print; Smith, Edward W.
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 18, 1928-02 -- 1928-04; MS036.001.040.00001 (Volume 40)
    Alpha Omicron Pi photos of members, p74-77; Alpha Tau Omega, pg 104-105.
    - Engineers in front of Robinson Hall, 1930; MS036.001.040.00001.04323; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 40)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 40, #6941, p. 14
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 17, 1928-01 -- 1928-02; MS036.001.041.00001 (Volume 41)
    - Jackson Glee Club at Goddard Chapel, 1926-02-15; MS036.001.041.00001.04324; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 41)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 41, #6906, p. 131
      Women; Students; photographic print; Black students; Jackson College; Jackson Glee Club
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 31, 1931-09 -- 1931-11; MS036.001.050.00001 (Volume 50)
    - Japanese students Shizue H. Komu and Ethel Hideko Omori, 1931-10-14; MS036.001.050.00001.03334; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 50)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 31, Box. No. 50, Pg. 51
      People; Students; photographic print; Komu, Shizue H.; Omori, Ethel Hideko; School of Medicine; New England Medical Center
    - The view of the campus from the chapel tower, 1931-10-22; MS036.001.050.00001.03341; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 50)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 31, Box No. 50, Pg. 85
      Views; Buildings; photographic print
    - Assistant to the Registrar Helen Beardsley (left) and Stenographic Assistant L. Helen Erb (right), 1931-10-22; MS036.001.050.00001.03458; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 31)